珍，希望这不会让你感到尴尬
但我发现评估新员工最好的方式
就是以严厉的目光凝视他们
— 所以！
— 所以
— 第一天！
— 对！
— 感到害怕？
— 是的……
— 不要害怕！
— 我其实没有害怕
你应该会感到害怕
— 嗯我是有那么一点点害怕
— 啊？别怕！
你说了算吧！
一定期待已久了吧！
是
我…… 非常期待……
— 可以开始了解……
— 我准备把你放到IT部门
因为你在简历里说你对计算机有很丰富的经验
我在我的简历中是有提到，确实。
我对整个计算机领域有着……
非常丰富的经验…… 你知道的，电子邮件……
发送邮件，接受邮件,
删除邮件...
– 我还能继续说下去
– 说下去！
万维网…… 使用鼠……
鼠标…… 用鼠标
单击…… 双击……
当然还有屏幕，键盘
那个放在地下的小东西……
— 硬盘？
— 对的
看来，你确实对你的工作十分了解
没别的问题了
我看好你，珍！
而且他们需要一个新的主管
太好了！
所以…… 那些将和我一起工作的人，
都怎么样呢？
标准的书呆子！
你好，I.T.
你有没有试过把它关掉再打开？
好，那么，侧面的按钮，是亮着的吗？
嗯，你需要把它打开！
那个按钮，把它打开？！
嗯…… 你…… 嗯……
你不会连怎么按按钮都不知道吧？
不，不是在衣服上的！
你好，I.T.？
Yeah?
你是否尝试过意外强制重启？
不不不！可以了！不，已经可以了，
我刚听到它启动了
不不不，那是它启动的声音
不是，那是它启动的……
对不起，你是从古代来的吗？
看起来是驱动程序通过修改系统调用表来挂钩函数
而这时重载它是不安全的
除非另一个线程正要插入那里
并执行它自己的任务
你也不想最终进入无效内存里面吧
你好？
Really? Really, why don't you come
down here and make me then?
What? Oh you think I'm afraid of you?
I'm not afraid of you!
You can come down here any time
and I'll be waiting for ya!
That told her!
Oh God, it's about time you got back,
it's been all go.
You had a job?
Girl on fifth...
你和她…… 一拍即合了吗？
Did you and her... hit it off?
定义“一拍即合”？
Define "hit it off"?
她在你修好她的电脑之后继续和你聊天吗？
Did she continue talking to you
once you'd fixed her computer?
没有……
No...
而且在我修她的电脑的时候，她把一个杯子放在我背上
And while I was working on it,
she rested a cup on my back.
— 不是吧？！
– No?!
—— 是的！
– Yep!
难以置信！
Unbelievable!
是的，他们对我们一点都不尊重，一点也没有！
Yeah, I mean they've not respect for us
up there, no respect whatsoever!
我们对他们来说只是干苦力的
We're all just drudgens to them.
对！
Yes!
如果有这么一个词叫“干苦力”
If there were such a thing as a drudgen,
那就是我们对他们的意义
that is what we'd be to them.
每当他们的打印机出问题的时候
It's like they're pally-wally
他们就像好朋友一样
when there's a problem
with their printer
但一旦问题解决了……
but once it's fixed...
他们就把我们抛在一边，就像隔夜的果酱一样！
They toss us away like yesterday's jam!
对！
Yes!
隔夜的果酱！
Yesterday's jam!
这就是我们对他们的意义！
That is what we are to them!
其实你知道吗？
Actually you know what?
这个说法并不太恰当……
That doesn't really work as a thing...
因为你知道的，果酱可以保存很久……
because you know, jam lasts for ages...
你好，I.T.？
Hello, I.T. ?
你有没有试过把它关掉再打开？
Have you tried turning it off
and on again?
中性厕所？你们有中性厕所，就像《艾莉的异想世界》里面那样？
Unisex toilets? You have unisex toilets,
like Ally McBeal?
这就是这个地方的情况，珍
That's the sort of place this is, Jen.
很多性感的人，不怎么工作…… 还有一些婚外情
A lot of sexy people not doing
much work... and having affairs.
哦我的天啊！看那个景色！
Oh my God! Look at that view!
I feel like I'm on top of the world.
Well Jen, this is where I leave you.
Floor 34.
Great sir, thank you.
OK. Where am I going?
y'y
All... the way down to the basement.
Good luck!
Get out of the lift...
– Oh. Won't be a tick!
– Oh my God!
Oh my God! Oh God! OK.
Hello?
Yes I believe it was Tolstoy who said...
Oh, it seems we have a visitor.
I'm sorry, myself and Morris
were just engaged
in quite a serious discussion
about books and such.
We didn't hear you come in.
Wait a second, you said it was
Tolstoy, he said what?
Oh never mind that now, Morris!
When have you read Tolstoy?
Shut up, Morris!
Why are you speaking that weird voice?
When did... I don't remember
this conversation at all!
Don't... don't let me disturb you,
I just wanted to come down....
Don't be silly you never dist...
Many people come down here to visit!
What are you talking about?
Who comes down? What people?
Why are you giving me
the secret signal to shut up?!
So... What can we do you for?
I'm the new head of this department.
Is this my office?
Why? What did she... Did she just say...
– I am the head of this department!
–  I thought I was.
It's one of us! Certainly not her!
I'm gonna sort this out...
Roy! You've got a head wound there...
Head wound!
Hi!
I don't wanna be rude or anything
but I wasn't informed of any changes
to this department.
Oh, did they not tell you about me?
No!
And we are perfectly fine down here,
thank you very much,
we're more than capable
of taking care of ourselves.
Sure... sure...
You know you're covered in blood?
Moss!
Amazon thingy.
Wicked!
I know what this is.
It's the new Harry Potter.
I got the child edition
and the adult edition
just to check that there are
no differences in the text.
Sorry but I'm not gonna be able
to deal with that woman!
Is nobody else going to get the phone?
I suppose I'll get it!
No, that is not a phone.
I'm gonna have a little lie down.
Come in!
Yeah, Denholm. Yeah, yeah.
No no no... No they've been fine so far.
Yeah. I think we're gonna get on great.
Yeah, I know.
All right then, now you take care.
All right, yeah I will, yeah.
Ok!
Ok, take care, take care!
Ok bye! Bye!
Oh, so, hello!
What can I do you fo...
What can I do for you?
Hello. I was just wondering...
Do you want me to connect up your phone?
No no no... No.
It's working.
I was just talking to Denholm.
But how?!
Oh do you mind... Do you mind
closing the door for me?
– Oh yeah, sure.
– Yeah, Ok.
Yeah. From the other side...
Of course.
– Like this?\
– That's it!
– With me on the...
– Thanks!
Are you all right?
Oh yes, Moss, I'm fine!
The nurse said I didn't do myself
any serious damage.
I'm standing over here!
I know, I know, I'm joking, I'm fine!
What we gonna do about her?
Well, I just went in, and she was having
a pretend conversation.
– Really?
– Yes.
She's a little bit weird...
to say the least.
What's that?
Oh just water.
Sometimes, I get a hot ear,
and this helps cool it down.
She is quite the oddbod...
Did you notice how
she didn't even get excited
when she saw this original ZX-IT 1?
Yeah, that was weird.
It's almost as if she doesn't know
anything about computers.
What?!
Look what you did!
Oh don't worry that's why
I always make 2 cups of tea.
Anyway, what were we talking about?
Oh, her not knowing anything
about computers.
What?!
I definitely want to get rid of her.
I agree yeah.
Ok, so, here's the plan:
A plan? Let me put on
my slightly larger glasses.
Ok, hit me!
– Ok. We go in...
– When?
You know, like in a minute.
Will that be enough time for me
to get to know the plan?
Yeah, you know what?
I shouldn't have used the word "plan"!
I... I've clearly gotten you
over-excited!
Would "steamed" be a better word?
Although that's just as exciting,
I might even use these.
All I was gonna say was...
We go in, I make up a load of bullocks
about computers
and we'll see if she picks up on it.
Yes. I can see why
you didn't want to use the word "plan".
Let me do the talk.
All right.
Ouh, Moss, Moss Moss!
Ok, we need to get this right, you know?
We... we need to stay calm.
We do not wanna go in there half-cocked.
Hang on, guys.
How can I help?
Well, we were just wondering
now that you're "The Boss",
would you like us to access
the data supplier
and connect you up to the matrix?
You just made all that up?
You don't know anything
about computers, admit it!
Will you stop trying to undermine me!
Now get in there,
and do some work, to do with computers!
I'll be in there in a minute
and check up on you!
Ok, lady!
You've won this round, but we can wait!
You will slip up one day,
and believe you me,
we will be there when you do!
There will be some piece of evidence
that will prove
without any shadow of a doubt
that you don't know
anything about computers.
What are you doing?
Plugging in your computer.
It might be something you say...
or something you do!
But when we notice this,
and believe me we will notice this,
there's gonna be a long way down
for you, sweet chicks!
He'll realize in a second...
I cannot believe you're going
to tell on me.
You're like a pair of horrible
old women.
What did she say?
She said we're like horrible old women.
She didn't!
Hey guys!
Ok, got something to tell me?
Yes, well, it's like this:
Look at you! My I.T. Team.
– Yeah.
– Team players each and every one of you.
Yeah, what she...
There's no room for people
who can't act in a team on my team!
Excuse me.
Hello?
What?!
Well if you can't work as a team,
you're all fired!
That's it, you heard me, fine!
Get your things and go!
Hello, Security?
Everyone on floor 4 is fired.
Escort them from the premises.
And do it as a team!
Remember you're a team, and if you can't
act as a team, you're fired too!
Dawn!
Get onto recruitment.
Tell them to look for a security team
that can work as team.
They may have to escort our
security team from the building,
for not acting like a team!
Team! Team team team team team!
I even love saying the word "team".
You probably think that's a picture
of my family?
It's the A-Team.
Body, Doyle, Tiger, the Jewellery Man!
All of them!
So what do you wanna tell me?
Well, it's just not working out.
– He's joking!
– But you said...
Not working out?
Oh no! No!
We are getting on like
a big house on fire!
– Yeah!
– My ear's getting hot!
No... You know what?
We should leave, now, because
you know, you're a busy man
and we've taken far too much
of your time.
Jen could you just get the door
for me there?
Absolutely Roy!
So why did you come here
in the first place?
We set up a voice activation system
on your computer.
I think you're gonna enjoy it.
It might just take a little while
to get the pitch right on the voice
but nonetheless, go ahead!
Thank you very much!
– Bye bye!
– Thank you!
How exciting!
Hello...
Hello computer!
Hello!
Hello... Hello computer...
What good are you?
You obviously don't know anything
about computers.
No but... OK.
But I can learn.
You know, I mean, for example Moss,
you could take me through
what you're doing right now.
I'd be delighted!
I'm just working on a very simple piece
of programming code.
I see...
Oh God, no, I'm lying again!
I didn't understand any of that!
I don't know anything
about computers, I mean...
I'm absolutely useless to you.
I might as well pack up and go home.
Hi! Is... Roy around?
Hello there little lady!
Are you lost?
How can I help you? I'm Roy.
You wanted me to come down?!
Well here I am!!
Not the face!!
Well maybe this will teach you
to treat people with
a little bit of respect!
Is it 'cos we spoke on the phone
earlier?
Oh my God! Are those Manolo's?
Yes!
They are gorgeous! Were they expensive?
No! Got them in a sale.
Oh God! Clever you!
I'm never lucky enough
to get a bargain myself.
Well, I should take you shopping.
Yeah, no that would be fantastic.
Oh I will give you a call.
Nice to meet you! Take care!
– Nice meeting you!
– Chairman! Wow!
You just diffuse that entire situation!
What situation?
Oh, that.. yeah!
Oh my God, does that happen a lot?
They're fairly regular,
the beatings, yes.
I'd say we're on a by-weekly beatings.
Ah it's not all that bad!
Ah, come on Roy! It's pretty bad...
Maybe I could help with this.
You know, I mean...
I'm a people person and...
people like you need a person
to deal with people...
a people person like me. Oh my God!
Ideas are coming!
Things are happening here!
Ok, Ok, what would you say here,
if I told you that I had a plan
to raise your profile upstairs by 100%.
What would you say?
I can't be done! You're crazy!
What would you say Roy?
Roy's passed out! Ok!
I need a felt-tip pen, and some paper.
PARTY - I.T. DEPT 5.45 TODAY
No no! Oh no, really really really,
that was a true story!
Unbelievable!
I said why we don't go out
with the I.T. guys more often?
– You're hilarious!
– Yes we are!
You guys should come down here
more often you know,
you should see this as a new era
for Reynholm Industries.
"A new era for Reynholm Industries!"
Do you know what! If you want
to hear something really funny,
a really funny story,
you should hear what happened
to Moss and I,
when we were so drunk in Amsterdam
that Moss lost his glasses!
Moss! Moss!
Come here! Come here!
Tell them that story about
when we were drunk in Amsterdam.
Really?
Yeah yeah yeah! Oh it's brilliant!
Oh this a great story,
you're gonna love it!
I'm just gonna get another box of wine!
Well go on, then.
All right.
– Well, one night, we were really drunk.
– Yeah.
And huh, we were so drunk
that we decided to hire prostitutes.
And when they arrived to the hotel,
we were too scared to do anything,
so we brought them to the fair.
Oh really nice! In the end,
they only charged us half.
But we did have to pay
for all the rides.
噢难道这不是最棒的故事吗？
Oh isn't that just the best story?
哦各位！
Oh, man!
你告诉过我不要把这件事告诉任何人
You told me to never tell that story
to anyone.
啊，你在说什么呢？
Well, what're you talking about?
这是一个绝妙的故事！
That's a brilliant story!
后来你几乎要走到水沟里去
And then you nearly walked
into the canal!
Has it got to that part
with the boatman?
你说的是我丢了我的眼镜的那个故事吗？
Do you mean the story
when I lost my glasses?
对啊！
Yes!
你觉得我说的是什么故事？
What story did you think I mean?
莫斯？
Moss?
你说了什么？！你说了什么？！
What did you say?! What did you say?!
这就很适合你们两个
It's all right for you two.
You're used to being social social piranhas...
我一般是个很受欢迎的人
I'm a very popular person usually.
之前那个，想用她的鞋子把我打死的女孩
That girl earlier, that tried
to beat me to death with her shoes,
有人有她的电话号码吗？
did anybody get her number?
讲道理这真是美好的一天，不是吗？
That was a nice day the fair, wasn't it?
With Brandy and Crystal!
你好，I.T.？
Hello I.T.?
嗯，你有没有试过把它关掉再打开？
Yeah. Have you tried turning it off
and on again?
你好！你好！
Hello! Hello!