Which means, which means...
a profit so far this year of...
1800 billion billions.
– Splendid!
This doesn't even include
the added revenue
arising for your take over of ITV!
ITV? I'd forgotten about ITV.
Brilliant!
Gentleman, when I first started
Reynholm Industries,
I had just two things
in my possession:
a dream and 6 million pounds.
Today, I have a business empire,
the like of which...
the world has never seen
the like of which.
Hope it doesn't sound arrogant
when I say...
that I am the greatest man
in the world!
Gentleman, to the future.
Oh, you don't have any glasses.
Just pretend.
– To the future!
Sorry to interrupt
but there are some policemen here,
they say they need to speak to you
about irregularities
in the pension fund.
I see. Could you make me a cup of tea,
please, Stephanie?
Nice.
–Isn't she a beauty?
– It's certainly a phone.
160 PPI screen.
Wi-Fi enables...
– Ask me what kind of phone I've got.
– What kind of phone have you got?
– It doesn't matter.
Voice recognition.
So let's say I wanted to call my mum,
I just have to say "mum",
and it calls her.
I don't need to do anything.
It's the dog's bollocks.
Mum, mum, no...
No, I'm sorry.
No, Moss said that.
Yeah, okay, I'll call you later, bye.
Only problem with it is that it's got
a very weedy vibrate setting.
I mean, watch this.
I mean, what is that?
– I'll sort it out.
– Oh, could you?
Just you know, welly up
the vibrator a bit.
Okay, all right.
Now, will you answer this question?
Are we still on this?
You keep interrupting!
We would've been done ages ago,
but you...
– All right, go on.
Question 39.
When was the last time you exercise?
The last time I exercised was never.
I'm still reeling
from your answer to question 12.
What was question 12?
You brush your teeth in the bath.
– So?
– That's where your balls are.
Okay, question 40.
Do you get your five fruit and veg?
I mean, I certainly try to...
I would say I probably do.
– A day.
– A what?
You're going to love this.
This website takes
all the information you gave me
and guess what it does?
It actually estimates
the date of your death!
– What?
– I know.
Unbelievable, isn't it?
– What? Wait a second.
I know about those!
Everyone knows about those!
All right, so you've already done it.
So, when's the big day?
No!
I haven't done it!
Why would I want to do it?
– I get March 2nd 2079.
– Oh, my God!
That's right, baby!
I've got 70 more years!
Okay, Moss, close that window!
– I do not wanna know!
– But I've written it all in now.
Moss!
I do not wanna know
the date of my death.
Close it.
Hello, IT, have you tried
turning it off and...
You know, I'm sick of saying that.
What do you want?
Okay, yeah, someone
will be up in a minute.
Maybe.
You looked!
You know!
You know when I'm going to die!
I do, yes.
– I told you not to look!
– I made a mistake.
When is it?
– You don't wanna know.
– You can't say that to me now!
My advice, Roy,
is to forget all about this.
What, how long more
they've given me, 20 years?
It's less than twenty?
You see, I don't think
this is taking into account leap years.
So that could well be
something to hang on to.
What does it say, Moss?
Does it say I'm already dead?
– No, that would be terrible.
– Thank God.
– It's Thursday.
– What?
– Thursday?
Again, remember, leap years.
It's Thursday!
Thursday the 3rd!
Although, not too late after noon,
so that gives you most of the day.
What? 3 p.m.!
– How could they be that specific?
– Yeah, it's silly.
Yeah.
These things are, at best,
79% accurate.
Oh, good.
I would take no further notice of it.
Yeah, you're right, it's silly.
I will take no further notice of it.
Apparently, there's something wrong with
all the computers on 7th. Who wants it?
Roy?
You look terrible. Are you ill?
I don't know.
These idiots disabled
the flipping firewall!
Yeah, hello, excuse me.
Thank you, some attention please.
I know you don't think it's "important"
or "cool" but there is
a ruddy good reason
why we put up anti-virus software
and firewalls.
It's because there are
a lot of dangerous things out there.
Jesus!
You know, calm down.
Just don't disable the firewalls.
Okay, 73', that's good, that's good.
And mum,
what age did Uncle Tony die?
32?
It was a car accident?
Brilliant!
Okay, no, I completely forgot... Okay.
Mum, I have to go.
Unbelievable,
some brainiac disabled his firewall
which means that all the computers
on floor 7 are teeming with viruses.
Plus, I've just had to walk all the way
down the mother fudging stairs
because the lift is broken, again.
Oh, my God.
– What?
– Oh, my God.
What? What it is?
Denholm is dead.
Oh, yes, and Denholm is dead.
Okay, everyone ready?
You look great.
We should go to more funerals.
Yeah, except, is there any chance
I could...
not go to this one?
– No, why?
It's just, you know, funerals.
So morbid.
Would you please forget
this website nonsense?
You are not going to die.
Come on, cheer up!
You're gonna ruin the funeral.
Yeah, you're right.
Pay no attention to me.
I'm being an idiot.
Dead man walking!
Very funny.
You crazy little bastard!
When did you last exercise, Jen?
No, you are not going to do it to me.
– Scared?
– No.
I happen to think
I have a good few years left.
I take plenty of exercise
and I haven't smoked for 3 years.
I didn't know you smoked.
I was on 40 a day by the end.
40 a day, that's 146 002 a decade.
Presuming at least two leap years.
How the flip do you give up?
Basically, pure self-control, Moss.
No, I'd never smoke again.
I'd rather lick a tramp.
Derek, hello.
Hello, Jen.
Thanks for printing out
those funeral announcements.
Oh, no, I enjoyed doing it.
You know, in a sad way.
– Can I have a word, please?
– Sure.
Hey, oh, my phone.
Oh cool, have you souped up?
Yeah, I totally pimped your phone,
girlfriend.
What set are you setting?
That is the lowest setting.
It shall come as no surprise to you
that I don't like this department.
Never have, never will.
I see no need for an IT department,
I would much rather use this basement
for something important.
Like a big toilet!
I have to say that actually,
it's a bit of a surprise.
– Really? I did send out a memo.
– I didn't get it.
– I had no idea you felt like this.
– Well, I do.
However, I am prepared to give you
another chance.
Another chance? But I didn't know
we'd already had a chance.
This should be the first chance.
You should give us this chance.
And then, another chance.
OK, I'll get it! Give me a call!
I got to put it up to 5.
I'm gonna put it in my pocket!
Put it up to 8!
I'm not gonna put it up to 8, Moss!
It'll blow my cock off.
– Come on, come on. Put it up!
– Okay, I'll put it up.
You do know
we are burying a great man today!
Did someone else die?
I mean, Mr. Reynholm!
Yeah.
"Did someone else die?"
Oh, I didn't know.
You have to be careful,
he's our new boss.
He hates us, he keeps saying
that there's no need
for an IT department.
– Why didn't anyone tell me this?
There was a memo.
It just said:
"I hate the IT Department."
Oh no, no, no!
You are not coming to the funeral,
Richmond!
What funeral?
– Has anyone got the right time?
– It's twenty to three.
I'll make it a quarter, too.
Why? Yes! Because that website said
you were going to die at 3pm, didn't it?
– Did it? I can't remember.
– How could you forget?
It clearly stated that
you were going to die, today.
At precisely 3:00.
Unless, it was tomorrow.
But no, it's today, at 3:00.
Well, would you put it
out of your mind?
Right, you're right, out of my mind.
Okay, there's Denholm's wife.
I never know what to say
to people at funeral.
Neither do I. I'm terrible.
Oh, just say "I'm sorry for your lost",
then move on.
– He'll be in our prayers.
– Thank you.
– Sorry for your loss.
Move on.
– Thank you.
It's not like you've lost a pen, is it?
It's so much worse.
Would you like a pen?
–I have this spare one.
– Oh, no, thank you.
– Please, take it.
– Why are you giving it to me?
I don't know.
It swings an under balance.
Death!
Death is coming!
Death is here...
Death is outside...
There's no escape.
I don't like the way
Derek's looking at us.
Who's that knocking at the door?
Yes...
It's death! Yet it'd be.
Is this normal?
Death came for Denholm
just as it will come for you.
Who will be next?
You?
Maybe you...
– We are gathered here to...
– What's wrong with you?
– ...past of a great man.
– Nothing.
A man...
...like us.
I've never seen a grand-father clock
in a church before.
Yet, the one was a second hand.
Yes, he had more money than...
most of us here today.
But did that make him a better man?
We know Denholm was a man of money.
Yes, he had more money...
than any of us here.
Oh, no! Jesus!
Jesus Christ!
Holy...!
Call me an ambulance!
I'm not f****** joking!
And get an ambulance!
Call me a f****** ambulance!
Oh, no, wait...
That's my phone!
I think that... It's...
Let's see if... I can't leave it.
I can't leave it. I'll turn it off.
I've just been set up.
Oh, God f***!
Go on!
Oh, it's gone to message.
Hey, Roy, nothing important!
Just wondering how the funeral went.
Call me back.
If we are all quite ready,
Denholm instructed that this short film
be played before the service.
You're all out of there!
You are out of there!
You're history!
Hello!
If you're watching this,
it means I'm dead, now.
And it's all thanks
to these little things.
– Wrong!
– Shut up!
Cigarettes have finally killed me.
Like they killed my father,
my father's father,
my mother's father, my mother,
and her father.
I just can't seem to give
the damn things up. I love them!
Sweet smoky cigarettes.
You delicious bastards!
Final clause, Stephanie,
could you categorise the personel files
alphabetically from now on?
That rhyming thing, this isn't working.
Also call Who's Who
and get them to update my entry.
Well, thanks everyone for coming!
Enjoy the rest of the funeral.
Well said, sir!
I will now ask Mr. Pippin
to read the eulogy.
I see a lot of faces out there.
Some of you I know, some of you
I hope to get to know better
over the coming months.
Some of you I probably won't be
seeing very much off, after today!
The reading of the eulogy
is a duty normally left
to the eldest child.
But, as you all know,
Denholm's son Douglas
mysteriously disappeared
after a lengthy court case, 7 years ago.
Let me start by reading this poem
that I saw
in the film Four Weddings and a Funeral.
"Stop... all the clocks."
Father!
– Tits!
– We're just a small church.
Unhappy priest!
Where is your God?
Where is your God now!
Here lies a great man!
A great man!
Father!
– Did I miss anything?
– They just started Denholm's eulogy.
You stink!
I just smoked a cigarette from a drain.
Well, who's this?
– Hi, I'm Douglas.
– Jen Barber.
Beautiful second name!
What're you doing after the funeral?
– Douglas!
– Speak, priest!
No, I'm a vic...
Your father prepared a second tape
in the event of your sudden arrival.
– A second tape?
I see...
Actually, I don't follow.
– I'll just put in on.
Hello again. If you're watching this,
it's because my son from my 1st marriage
has arrived,
caused a scene, and is currently
chatting up some nearby trouble.
Quiet, woman!
I have something important
to tell you.
I'm here, papa!
Reynholm Industries is now yours.
– My Lord, thank you father.
– But it's yours at a price.
I want you to promise me now,
in front of all your new employees,
that you will never again
become embroiled
in a sexual harassment case
that dangers the company.
– I promise, father.
There's one more thing,
but it's for your ears only.
So, I want you to stop the tape,
take it home,
and watch it again later in private.
– But these are my new family, father.
I have no secrets from them!
OK, Douglas. Now we're alone,
I can speak frankly.
You may receive a visit
from the police at some point
concerning irregularities
in the pension fund.
Turn that off.
I've been using a very creative
accountant recently released from jail
to manage what I call the suck fund!
– Where is the remote?
– Now, the suck fund...
– I'll do it myself!
Good bye, father!
Right, I'm off.
I'll see you all on Monday.
Douglas! Sorry,
I didn't mean to. Derek Pippin!
I worked very closely with your father.
Derek, good to meet you.
I'm afraid I'll be bringing in my own
people, so you're immediately fired.
Okay, good luck everyone, and...
I'll see you later.
– ...and you are ready to go!
– Brilliant!
Thank you, computer man!
I'm told my father was particularly
proud of the IT department.
Run by a dynamic go-getter,
a genius, and a man from Ireland!
One last thing.
How do I erase files like this one here,
marked pensions?
– Just like this.
– All gone!
Wonderful. Thanks, guys.
I'll be working very closely
with your department.
And I have a feeling I'll be needing you
for a lot more than
just deleting incriminating files.
I just mean files.
– OK, we'd better be off.
– By the way...
Where's that ootsie-tootsie
humdinging-coochie mama-boss of yours?
She went home early.
She said she had some catching up to do.
One last thing.
I sorted out this for you.
Now, I'm afraid the vibrate setting
is still a little weedy.
So, you may wanna
put it all the way up to ten.
Ten!
Shall I do...
...done...
...and done!
Okay, bye-bye...
Sorry about this, old man!
Oh, yes.
Now, I like that!
Nearly at the station!