Wow! That's quite something.
Quite an honour.
— I know.
— They must be very impressed with you.
I didn't even know they had
an Employee of the Month thing here.
— Really? I thought you won it once.
— No, everyone thought I was dead.
Aha.
Employee... of the Month.
Yeah, it's a valued title.
— Have you ever won it?
— Er, no. No, I haven't.
I don't know, Jen,
sometimes I think
it's because I just
want it so damn much!
I am the Employee of the Month.
And yet, to a casual
observer, it would
appear that you do
very little around here.
Yeah. They must have seen through that.
I think someone up there
must have sensed something in me,
something I've always known
was there — a greatness?
No, I'm not saying that,
but... well, something.
Yeah! Yeah, I'm sensing something.
Don't worry,
I won't let it go to my head.
Guess who's won
Employee of the Month.
— Roy.
— No.
— Richmond.
— Harry.
— Who's Harry?
— The postman.
— No.
— Me.
— I said Roy, right? Richmond.
— Meeeee!
— Oh! Oh, about time!
— Yeah.
— Whatever happened to Richmond?
— He got scurvy.
Be more specific.
I'm trying to build up
a picture of your role
in Reynholm Industries.
Well, I'm the boss,
head honcho, el numero uno,
Mr Big, the Godfather,
Lord of the Rings,
the Bourne Identity,
er... Taxi Driver,
Jaws.
I forgot the question quite
a while back. Who are you again?
I'm April Shepherd. You're being made
Richest magazine's Man of the Year.
— I'm doing the profile.
— Oh, yes, that's right.
You're the boss —
what does that entail?
Oh, many things.
This morning,
for instance, I had to choose
the Employee
of the Month from the box.
May I ask,
what are you doing on that pad?
One of my little hobbies
is caricature.
Sometimes I like to sketch someone
as I'm talking to them.
— May I?
— Well, I'm not very good.
I'm no Truman Capote.
Great. OK, erm... I'll tell you what,
let's just do some quickfire questions.
Maybe they'll give me an insight
into «the real you.»
OK.
Who is your favourite
person from history?
Sherlock Holmes.
— Well, he's fictional.
— Whoa!
I think you'd better
check your facts there. Fictional?
Who took care
of the business with
the giant dog that was
eating everybody?
It wasn't Watson.
Don't tell me,
I suppose he was fictional too?
Maybe there was no giant dog.
No, no, I think you're playing games
with me, young lady!
OK, then, favourite
fictional character?
Oh... the Elephant Man.
Tell you what, let me
widen the question out.
Favourite popular figure?
— Churchill.
— What is it you like about him?
I love the way he says:
«Oh, yes! Oh, yes!»
I think perhaps it's you
who's playing games with me.
You're a very surprising
man, Mr Reynholm.
Yes...
I am a surprising man.
April, may I take you to dinner?
— Oh, I don't think I could possibly...
— In Paris.
— Paris?!
— Paris, yes.
It's the name
of a new restaurant in Hull.
That's right, we're going to Hull!
Hey, Roy, come over here.
Look at this.
«The biggest adventure
you can ever take
is to live the life
of your dreams» —
Oprah Winfrey»?!
I suppose that is the biggest adventure.
Guys, come on in.
Sit down.
— Is this a new desk?
— Yeah.
I thought I needed
some new furniture, so
I got some stuff from
upstairs. Sit down.
I just thought, what with
all this extra attention
on us... on me,
it might be worth
looking at ourselves and
saying, «Hey, am I
really giving it 110%?»
«And if not, why not?
What the heck is wrong
with me? Am I mentally
ill or something?»
Roy, let's start with you.
When you're upstairs,
fiddling about with compu-ters,
would it hurt to smile?
Don't you realise
what a difference that would make? Eh?
Come on, let's see a smile now.
Come on.
No, more warmth. Warmer.
You're just showing more teeth.
That's not warmth.
I would say that's
more of a threatening look, actually.
I'll tell you what, Roy, keep at it.
That's your homework. Moss...
So, what's your
speech going to be about?
What speech?
Every Employee
of the Month has to give
a speech in
their area of expertise.
Which for you is «compu-ters».
— Where do I have to...?
— At the monthly shareholders' meeting.
— When do I have to...?
— Friday.
— What time...?
— Morning.
How's that?
— What's up, guys?
— All right, Jen?
Ohhhhh... God!
— Just writing a speech.
— Oh, yeah, that's right.
— How's that going?
— Good, good, good, good, good, good.
You know, I was thinking...
if there's anything
you guys want
I can put it in,
it's no problem.
Oh! Oh, yeah.
Hm, interesting.
Erm, is there anything you'd like to say
to the shareholders, Moss?
— Just say hi.
— Say hi from us.
— OK.
— I love this.
How many more times
is she going to come in?
Maybe it'd be a good idea
if you two contributed to this.
Oh, yeah? Why?
I think it would give you experience
in writing a speech for a public figure.
Well, obviously,
in our line of work that would be handy.
But you know what, Jen?
I'm actually snowed under here.
Wait a second. Wait a second!
— Oh! Oh, what are we doing?!
— Huh?
— We should totally write that speech!
— Why?
— OK, offer to write the speech for Jen.
— No.
She'll know something's up if I do it.
— You have to do it.
— Why would I do that?
— Moss, do you trust me?
— No.
— Do you trust me?
If you trust me,
then offer to write that speech.
I. Don't. Trust. You.
Hello?
I feel really bad,
having all the fun writing this speech.
Do it.
Offer, offer, offer.
Well, I suppose
we could write the speech
so that, you know, you look like
you know what you're talking about.
Thanks. I'm off for lunch.
Leave it on my desk.
My God!
I know.
That's brilliant!
So now you understand why
we have to write that speech for Jen.
She will say anything we tell her to.
We can put any
old bollocks in that
speech, and she shall repeat it.
It's going to be hilarious.
Sometimes I could kiss your mind, Roy!
OK, so let's just... I don't know,
let's just throw around a few ideas.
— OK, let's do it.
— OK.
Ooh! Could we tell her that there's
an apple inside every Apple Mac?
— It's good.
— Yeah.
We could say that
Bill Gates is called
Bill Gates because
he owns a lot of gates.
Hm! That's good.
It's not quite punchy enough.
And it's probably true now anyway —
I'll bet he does own a lot of gates.
He probably does.
It's got to be something big.
I think I may have it.
What?
You best put seatbelts
on your ears, Roy,
cos I'm going to take them
for the ride of their lives.
— Delightful.
— Oh, no, no, no. You're silly.
Do you know, I've never been
so enchanted by a woman in all my life.
What's your name again?
I know you told me.
— April.
— Ah, what a charming name.
Always been one of my favourites.
April... after dinner, would you do me
the honour of accompanying me to my bed?
— Oh. Erm...
— No, I've said too much!
I've let my heart overpower my head,
which is my wont.
But I don't care.
I find you enchanting.
And there's a condom machine
in the toilet — I've checked.
I'm very flattered,
Douglas, but, erm...
there's a problem,
something I should tell you.
— Go on.
— Erm...
I have a secret.
I could dance around
the subject, but I
like you, I want to
be straight with you.
Oh?
Erm...
I used to be a man, Douglas.
I used to be a man.
I wish there was
an easier way of saying
that, but believe
me, there's not.
I've had a lot of hormone therapy
and a number of operations.
I'm really sorry.
I... I hope you don't
feel I deceived you.
I understand if you would rather I left.
I don't care.
What?!
Doesn't bother me.
Doesn't bother you at all?
It takes all sorts to make a world.
Wow!
— It bothers most men.
— I'm not most men.
And the offer still stands.
Are you up for it?
Oh!
Amazing! Just amazing.
You liked it?
You really know your
way around that area.
Well...
Tell me, what are you doing
tomorrow night, April?
I was thinking of staying in
and watching the darts.
You've read my mind.
What is it?
This, Jen... is the internet.
— What?
— That's right.
This is the internet?
— The whole internet?
— Yep.
I asked for a loan of it
so that you could use it in your speech.
It's so small!
That's one of the
surprising things about it.
Hang on, it doesn't have
any wires or anything.
It's wireless.
Oh, yes, everything's wireless
nowadays, isn't it?
I can really use it in my speech?
What if someone needs it?
People will still be able to go online.
It will still work.
Oh, good.
I tell you, you
present this to the
shareholders and you
will get quite a response.
Can I touch it?
Oh! It's so light!
Of course it is.
The internet doesn't weigh anything.
No, of course it doesn't.
Hey!
What is Jen doing with the internet?!
Moss said I could use it for my speech.
Are you insane?!
— What if she drops it?
— I won't drop it. I'll look after it.
No! No, no, no, no, no, Jen.
No, this... this needs to go
straight back to Big Ben.
— Big Ben?
— Yep, it goes on top of Big Ben.
That's where you get the best reception.
I promise I won't let
anything happen to it.
No, Jen, I'm sorry.
The elders of the internet
would never stand for it.
No, Roy, I spoke to the elders
of the internet
not one hour ago.
I told them about Jen winning
Employee of the Month.
They were so impressed that they wanted
to do whatever they could to help.
Wait a minute!
The elders of the internet?
The elders of the
internet know who I am?!
You've got to let me have it!
No, Jen.
I'm sorry, it's just too risky.
— Oh, please, Roy?
— Oh...
Well... Moss, has it been
completely demagnetised?
By Stephen Hawking himself.
Who sends his congratulations,
by the way.
Well, if it's OK with the Hawk...
So can I have it?
You can.
— Oh, don't forget your speech.
— Thank you.
— Shh!
Slowly.
April, these past few days
have been like a dream.
Usually, I can't wait to get away
from a woman once I've ejaculated.
But with you...
I don't know, I feel alive.
— April, I love you.
— What?!
That's right.
I totally love the bloody arse off you.
Oh, Douglas, I love you too!
Oh, poppet... to think
when we met you
were so worried that
you came from Iran.
— What?
— When we met.
As if I'd be worried
about something like that.
I don't care where you're from —
Iran, France...
Doesn't bother me.
I'm very modern.
I'm not from Iran.
Well, you said
something along those lines.
No, not «Iran», «a man».
I said, «I used to be a man.»
You used to be a man?!
Yes!
Oh, God!
Well, we have a very interesting talk
lined up for today.
Our Employee of the Month
and computer expert Jen Barber
has kindly agreed to say a few words
about her role in the IT department.
Speaking as someone
who doesn't know the difference
between a laptop and, erm...
the larger one,
I'm certainly looking forward
to hearing what she has to say.
Good morning.
When I was asked to give a speech
about what it is I do and everything...
I was very excited.
«At last,» I thought,
«a chance to explain
the wonders of
technology to...
ordinary folk.»
But then I thought,
«Who wants to listen
to a boring old speech?»
Wouldn't it be better
if I could actually
bring one of these
wonders in to show you?
Say, I don't know... the internet.
I think it would, and I have.
Ladies and
gentlemen,
I'd like to present to you...
the internet!
Oh, please, no flash photography.
You'll harm the internet.
— Ladies and gentlemen...
— Why is no one laughing?
... if anything were
to happen to this box,
the world as we know it
would fall into chaos,
planes would drop from
the sky like tables,
society would tear itself apart
like an angry child with a napkin.
Man's primeval
instinct to survive at
any cost would lead
to terrible violence.
So, please, no flash photography.
I must say,
this is all very impressive, Douglas.
— So what exactly are you working on?
— I don't know.
April... we need to talk.
Oh, darling,
couldn't we do this at home?
I was hoping we could get shitfaced
and watch the telly.
There'll no more getting shitfaced
and watching the telly,
there'll be no more
Steven Seagal marathons,
and there'll be no more
paintballing weekends.
I'm afraid our adventure
has come to an end.
— What?! But... but why?
— It's not you, it's me.
No, actually,
it's not me, it is you.
I'm sorry.
You don't think of me
as a woman, do you?
What? Of course I do.
It bothers you that
I used to be a man!
No!
I love that you used to be a man —
it's your thing.
I love thinking about
that operation that you had.
Oh, please!
Look at me — I am a woman.
— This is a woman in front of you!
— Excuse me.
I am a woman!
— You're tearing me apart.
— Please, Douglas.
I'm sorry, it's beyond my control.
Please, Douglas. Please!
Just go.
You're making this harder for me.
You...!
How could you do this?
How could you do this to me?!
You bastard!
... and that's what
the flashing light is for.
— Any more?
— Is it heavy?
Is it... That's a bit
of a silly question —
the internet doesn't
weigh anything.
Well, OK, guys,
I guess I should wrap it up.
— Aw...
— No, no, I really have to finish up.
More! More! More!
Guys!
Oh, my God, you really like me.
— This really isn't that funny.
— I know. It's terrible.
I thought at least we'd get a good story
out of it, something we'd remember.
It's over, April!
Jesus!
The internet!
We're all going to die!
Everybody stay calm.
Wait for me! Wait!
He needs to hold his nerve now.
He's done it!
But it's not the same!
Oh, April!
Субтитры подготовлены студией FOCS.