«The IT Crowd»:
season 4, episode 1
Jen, have a listen to this.
Moss, have you
seen the newsletter?
Does this sound mysterious?
Yeah, yeah, it's quite mysterious.
I was hoping for ruddy mysterious.
It's fairly mysterious.
Compiling a playlist for
a role-playing game I'm hosting.
Important to get the right atmos.
Okay, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Kind of a Dungeons and Dragons thing.
Is this something to do with sex?
Far from it, Jen.
No, you see, in role-playing,
one person is a dungeon master,
or game master, or keeper.
He or she controls the world
and tells the players
what they're experiencing,
whether battling a coal monster,
or just kicking back in a smelly old
tavern with some roguish elves.
Played over a few hours,
it uses dice rolls to determine
the outcome of events.
Unlike most board games
you might be familiar with,
role-playing games often
use a 20-sided dice.
– Moss?
– Yeah.
I want to stop listening to this.
I completely understand.
So, in the world
we actually live in,
a post has opened up
for Entertainments Manager.
I could do that. That sounds great.
Better than whatever this job is.
Entertainments Manager.
It's not for you, Jen.
What? Organising cultural events
for visiting business partners,
that is so me.
It's not though.
It's really not for you.
What am I talking to you for?
Where's Roy?
Not in yet.
Is he still moping about
after that girl?
Worse than ever.
Thank God he can't play guitar.
Have you seen the pictures?
Pictures?
There's more than one of these?
Yeah, there's a buttload.
And she's Photoshopped
out of all of them.
Yeah, it's like someone
broke up with Stalin.
It's such a shame.
I've never seen him happier
than the last few months. And now...
– Hi, Roy!
– Hi, Roy/
It's okay, you're obviously
talking about me.
– No, no...
– It's fine.
I realise I haven't been the
easiest person to be around
the last few weeks.
But I really feel like
I've turned the corner now.
I really do.
So if we can all just
carry on as normal...
My God, my God!
I feel like I've come out
the other side of it now.
So, everything's going to be OK
from here on in...
My heart hurts!
You do seem better than yesterday.
But Roy, you've got
to snap out of this.
I know, I know.
Some things just don't work out.
I know you're not used to being
in a long-term relationship.
It's really rare for me.
It's so rare.
But take it from me,
most of them just don't work out.
She's right, Roy.
And how would you know?
I do all right.
When?
Well, if you must know,
I met a girl on holiday.
They're always on holiday,
aren't they, Moss?
Shut up, Dumpo,
the elephant who got dumped!
– Hey, hey!
– Well...
No, it's okay. I'm all right.
I mean, I'm still a bit...
She never said goodbye,
so, I just kind of...
It still just hurts just a little bit
whenever I think about her.
So. I guess all I have to do is just
never think about her. Simples!
She used to love that ad.
It's not for you, Jen.
What, why not?
Entertainments Manager?
Do you know what that involves?
From what I can gather
it's organising cultural events
for out-of-town business partners.
That's right. Yes, yes.
It's not for you.
But as fas as I can see,
it won't interfere
with my duties
in the IT department.
And I love culture. I've seen
We Will Rock You four times.
Well, Jen, I'd love to help you,
but traditionally the role
of Entertainments Manager
has always been held by a man.
Mr. Reynholm,
I don't need to remind you
of the report that denounced
Reynholm Industries
as an institutionally sexist
organisation.
Now, you hold on a minute,
sugar tits!
Everyone saw through that report.
I even got that award
off those feminists.
The one shaped like
the ice-cream fellow.
That's a «Shithead of The Year» award.
It actually says it on the base
«Shithead of The Year».
Did you not read the base?
– God!
– Women!
What are they? Who knows?
Don't do this.
Can't live with them,
can't find them sometimes.
What's going on
in their little heads?
Don't ask me, I'm not a flippin'
women psychiatrist.
But I have learned one or two things
from conversations with my mother.
No, no, Moss, please,
don't go any further,
just stop right there.
You're no good at this kind of thing,
Moss, you'll just make it worse.
Sorry, it's just
I've never seen you like this.
I know. But I'll be fine.
I will. It's just...
You can't help with this.
You just can't.
I've got it. I've got the job.
What?
Douglas gave me the job
so I'd stop talking.
Jen's Entertainments Manager.
It's not for you, Jen.
Why does everyone keep saying that?
What happened to Gerry?
Massive heart attack.
I'm not surprised.
Why are you not surprised?
Why is it not for me?
Gerry was the... He was the
company Fredo. You're the new Fredo.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Fredo, from the Godfather.
Who's Fredo again?
Who's he in it?
He's the brother, whose job it is to
take out-of-town businessmen and...
Show them a good time, yeah,
that's what I have to do.
I was thinking West End show...
No, no, Jen, I don't think
you understand.
These men are going to expect
a lot more than a West End show.
Fredo, Jen, he was...
He was sort of a pimp.
Shut up.
– Wasn't he, Moss?
– What?
Fredo, in the film,
he was essentially a pimp.
No, he took the ring to Mordor.
Fredo was a pimp.
No, no, that film was the '70s.
Things are different now.
Businessmen are different.
Anyway, enough about our balls.
Gentleman, I'd like you to meet Jen.
No, no, no, Jen's
our new Entertainments Manager.
But she's a woman, isn't she?
Jen, I'd like you to meet
an old friend of mine, Phil.
And two men named John.
What are you up to, Reynholm?
Don't you worry, Phil.
Jen may look like an old maid
holding pennies in her arse,
but she knows the sleaziest routes
round this old town
I like to call Londinius.
And I'm sure she's planned something
suitably raucous for you reprobates.
Yes, yes, I have tickets for
a wonderful show in the West End.
As long as it
doesn't have subtitles.
Subtitles, no.
What's got subtitles?!
– This thing she's bringing us to.
– Subtitles? God!
I can't read while I'm also
trying to see things.
No, no, it's a show, it's a show.
There's no subtitles.
I hate subtitles.
What happened to Gerry?
His heart exploded.
Brilliant!
No, he's quite seriously ill.
That's classic Gerry.
Gerry wouldn't have brought us
to something with subtitles.
There's no subtitles, it's a show.
Come on, Jen, what type of show?
Well, yes, well it's very raunchy.
Yes, I don't think
you'll be disappointed.
Women in it?
Yes, it's an all-woman show.
It's very rude.
An all-woman show?
And it's rude.
Eiffel Tower!
I'm so sorry,
I really can't apologise enough.
I've never been
so embarrassed in my life.
That woman was in EastEnders,
how dare you humiliate her?!
It's not our fault
you took us to something
called The Vagina Monologues.
You get there,
and it's just women talking.
False advertising.
Look, we're in town
for five more days.
You better have something
proper for us to do.
Next time you take us to something
about talking fannies,
it better be about talking fannies.
I know you had good reasons
for giving me this award.
I should never have done
that interview.
But that journalist had an agenda.
There's more.
«Women are a kind of savage animal,
who men have civilised
with their insatiable sexuality».
What don't you like about that?
«Women are essentially
no different from radiators».
«I like my women
like I like my toast, hot...»
And consumable with butter.
You don't have to remind me.
I'm all too familiar
with my misguided words.
Ladies, listen,
no-one can mistake me for Gok Wan.
I've an old-fashioned mindset,
but damn it, at least I try.
And Reynholm Industries is changing,
ladies, for the better.
The glass ceiling
is now a glass floor.
The women are floating above it,
and the men are just
looking up at them.
So, what do you want from us?
What?
Please take that award back
and give it to somebody else.
Mr. Reynholm, I really need
to talk to you about something.
Jen, I'd like you to meet
some very special woman.
– No, no, no!
– What?
Mr. Reynholm, I will not
work with prostitutes.
No, no, no, these are feminists.
You can dress it up
however you like,
they still sleep with men for money.
I'm sorry, no offence.
But I don't charge
for these potatoes.
And I don't like women who do.
Don't listen to her!
The bitch is crazy.
Douglas wants me
to see out the week.
A whole week in the
company of those idiots.
Culture's out, restaurants are out.
God, this is a nightmare.
Men!
What are they like? With their
bawdy talk and rough-housing,
and their wandering hands,
and breath in the morning.
I'd like to see them
have the babies.
What are you getting at, Moss?
Well, unless I'm very much mistaken,
this seems to be a problem for
which you need the male perspective.
Do you know any men?
You want a good time, right?
One that walks on the wild side
without compromising
your principles?
Yeah, that's exactly what I want.
Then you got it, baby!
...which is why the game needs
a 20-sided dice.
I've not understood a word
you've just said.
What is it?
Some sort of computer game?
In a sense, except it uses the
most powerful processor known to man.
The human mind.
But you're not playing.
I'm not a player.
But I am playing.
He sort of tells us
what's happening.
I will be your guide.
Through my words, you will
experience the land of Elfenheart.
From the mighty mountains that
border the Goblin Wastelands.
To the sewers that run like a spider
web through the city of Jandor.
I, gentlemen, will be your eyes.
I will be everyone you meet.
Every creature you encounter,
every trap you spring.
What about him?
What's this business with the face
like a slapped arse?
I'm sorry, I just came out of
a long-term relationship, so...
It doesn't...
She was the greatest woman
I've ever met and I'm never
going to see her again.
But it's fine, I mean,
she never said goodbye.
I'm not going
to bore you with it.
See that you bloody don't!
I still don't understand
what this game is!
It seems gay.
Are dragons gay, Phil?
Mighty warrior priests wielding
golden staffs.
I suppose they're gay too?
Here are your character sheets.
John One, you're a unicorn man.
John Two, you're a wood fairy.
And Phil, you're
the Gypsy assassin, Esmerelda.
I'm a woman?
I don't think I want to be a woman.
Just go with it.
It will end.
So, gentlemen, are you prepared
to open the doors to your mind
and travel to worlds
hitherto undreamed of?
Look at those fun bags.
Everybody doing okay, yeah?
You good for drinks?
Loosen up.
It's a role-playing party.
Jen, can I have a word?
I don't think I want
to hang with these guys.
Come on, Phil!
These guys are the best.
They're going to do things
tonight, that'll blow your mind.
Really?
Look at them.
They're young, they're keen.
And all they want to do
is show you a good time.
So get back there before
you hurt their feelings.
Could I steal
the lovely Roy for a sec?
It's just him in all of these.
Thanks, Jen, that was
all getting a little bit...
– What do you think you're doing?
– What?
Bringing everyone
down with your private life.
They don't want to know about
your miserable private life.
They're here for a good time.
Look at that face.
Who'd want to
role-play with that face?
I'm sorry Jen... I just...
I'm not feeling it tonight.
Then fake it, sweetheart, yeah?
We're getting good money for this.
Don't you want to get
the deposit for a flat,
leave those bad memories behind?
– Yeah.
– Yeah?
– I'll try harder, Jen.
– Okay.
Good girl.
Get back there and show
those Johns a good time.
Well, that cleaned the pipes.
I've got to thank you, Miranda,
for giving me a second chance.
Don't mention it. Although you
do know I don't have the authority
to take back the award myself?
What?
No, we all make mistakes.
And you intrigue me.
Something tells me there's
more to you than meets the eye.
Do you mean the rumours
that I killed my wife?
No. Are there rumours?
No.
There were rumours that there was a
rumour, but that was just bullshit.
I didn't like the way the nominations
came from inside your company.
Inside my company?
Yeah, one of the women from
the IT department faxed a dossier
of your behaviour over
the last 12 months.
One of the women
in the IT department?
Oh, sorry, Phil.
Heal All is probably the worst spell
you could have used.
The sound of your low-level magic
attracts the attention
of the palace guards.
Damn it!
One comes through the door.
Throwing knife.
Are you sure?
Quite a low damage.
I have a plus 40%
chance of a critical.
Remember the talking bunny that
gave me that magic bracelet?
Yeah, that bunny thing
gave him that thing.
You're absolutely right. Roll 'em.
– Yes!
Direct hit.
The knife cleaves his head in twain
and some of his brains runneth
down John Two's invisibility cloak.
Eiffel Tower!
Unfortunately, he wasn't alone.
Dammit!
'Tis the dreaded Imperial Guard,
the cruellest of all
of Queen Elisa's troops.
At their head
someone you recognise.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't the adventurers who
have been causing me all this bother.
Lucius Santana!
The very same.
Stand your men down, Lucius!
We have no quarrel with you!
Quarrel? I just came to see how a
mismatched bunch of raggle taggle
adventurers bested some of the
deadliest criminals in Crackenwood.
That's us!
You have my thanks.
And if you ever want to join
the Palace Guard,
you know where I am.
The Palace Guard?
You have my sword.
And my staff.
And my bunny bracelet.
And whatever it is that I have.
The mist clears.
You see alone, female figure.
That's ruddy mysterious.
Hello, Darkharden.
Hello.
Who goes there?
It is I, Queen Elisa Eldridge
of the Elves,
who cruelly jilted you
not three moons ago.
Don't do this.
Just go with it, Roy.
Hello, my queen.
How are you?
I'm fine.
You look well.
So do you... Does she?
– Yes, she does, actually.
– Does she?
So, what are you up to?
You know just...
Just keeping busy.
Missing you a little bit.
Yourself?
Usual boring pageantry.
You know how the people of
Pippsiehollow love a parade.
What are you doing here?
Sorry.
Sorry. Bear with me.
Bear with me. Bear with me.
I sense a sadness in you.
It's just hard.
You know?
I miss you.
I can still smell you on our pillow.
When I close my eyes,
it's still your face I see.
It's just hard.
You were here
and then you were gone.
What do you want?
It was not easy for me
to come here, Darkharden.
But I had one thing
I felt I needed to say to you.
Goodbye.
Brilliant night! Brilliant!
I can't believe I've never tried
role-playing games before.
I'm going to go home and tell
the whole rugby club about it.
Roy and Moss did not disappoint?
They did not.
I'd like to see them again.
Thank you, Douglas.
That's one special little
lady you've got there.
I'm glad Jerry died.
Eiffel Tower!
Eiffel Tower! Eiffel Tower!
– Eiffel Tower!
Before you go, Jen,
I know it was you.
You broke my heart.
You broke my heart!
That's right.
That's right!
Shut up!
You've cheered up.
Yeah, I'm feeling
a lot better now, Jen, thanks.
Thanks to a certain Elfin queen.
What happened to Fredo, in the film?
The Godfather has him killed.
I'm going to go home.
I'm not feeling too good.
Problem solved!
Субтитры подготовлены студией FOCS